Curriculum Vitae Of LAWRENCE CORRAYA

Email: lawrence.corraya05@gmail.com

Contact: +8801675381065



Career Objective:

I'm hardworking and honest. I have a strong analytical mind and a passionate heart for success to be the best for all the organizations by serving in any multinational company with integrity. Having around eight years of experience in Administrative & Human Resource sector.

Employment History Details:

Organization' Name:

RMG Sustainability Council (RSC)

Position: HR & Administrative Support Officer

Duration : June,2020 to till date **Company Location :** Dhaka

Duties/Responsibilities:

- Provide support to maintain employee human resource management records and related documentation.
- Provide support to manage employee attendance and leave utilization records and associated database through RSC's HR software.
- Ensure staff recruitment process and departure protocol.
- Liaise and manage relations with employees' medical/ other insurance service providers.
- Oversee the work of contracted serviceperson such as drivers, cleaners, guards and coordinate with the vendors on associated issues.
- Oversee ordering and purchasing of office supplies and equipment in accordance with RSC procurement policies.
- Maintain various administrative and financial records and files.
- Accurately maintain and continually update RSC inventory, condition of equipment, and equipment tagging system and lists.
- Make travel arrangements, hotel reservations and other logistics for various in-country and international missions to the RSC.
- Organize preparations and execute logistics for RSC meetings, programs, and other similar activities.
- Be responsible for keeping RSC's factory-level union information up-to-date in FFC and other RSC data receptacles.
- Perform other related duties as requested or assigned by the GM and/or ED.

Organization's Name:

Stichting Bangladesh Accord Foundation

Position: Administrative Assistant

Duration: February, 2014 to May, 2020

Company Location: Dhaka

Duties/Responsibilities:

- Ensure staff recruitment process and departure protocol.
- Keep records office employee's leave and attendance.
- Maintain staff's medical insurance.
- Maintain personnel document filing system.
- Liaise with external partners such as Brand Signatory, Trade Union, Insurance and Vendors.
- Arrange and support Seminar, Training, Webinar, Yearly performance appraisal/evaluation and Annual Retreat.
- Assist monthly payroll and other benefits.
- Assist the procurement, cost comparisons and receiving bids/quotations for the necessary purchase and service related to office and operation's needs.
- Assist the logistic support for any national and international programs and activities.
- Provide visa processing support to foreign officials.
- Make travel arrangement, hotel reservations and other logistics for various in-country and international missions.
- Maintain Store inventory and library.
- Handle phone calls, visitors and courier services.
- Maintain office supporting staffs and keep clean environment.
- Ensure the vehicle management related service.
- Ensure safety and security of the office premises and resource.
- Petty Cash
- Checking daily bills & Payment.
- Prepared daily Voucher.
- Banking deposit & withdrawal.

Organization's Name:

Bangladesh German Chamber of Commerce & Industry Ltd.

Position : Junior Executive Trade & Research

Duration: May, 2011 to October, 2011

Company Location: Dhaka

Duties/Responsibilities:

- Business inquiry.
- Foreign delegates & members dealing.
- Membership fee collection (yearly, miscellaneous fee).
- Organize the monthly Business Lunch of BGCCI.
- To collect update all kinds of information of a member and company.
- To maintain liaison for purpose of The German Trade Show 2011.
- Backup support for telephone operator.

- Promoting Bangladesh.
- Attend meeting and write meeting minutes.
- Perform other relevant duties as requested by the supervisor.

Organization's Name: The Dhaka Christian Co-operative Credit Union Ltd; Dhaka

Company Location: Dhaka

Department : Secretary Section & Accounts Section

Position: Trainee (Under Student Program)

Duration: June, 2005 to July, 2007

Duties/Responsibilities:

• Serve as first contact point for visitors.

- Receive, transfer and make telephone calls through the PABX system for Head of Accounts.
- Receive and send faxes.
- Receive/dispatch mail & materials and route them to the proper person (domestic courier, DHL, Office pouch).
- Handle scheduling requirements of conference and training room.
- Daily cash collection
- Voucher Sorting.
- Assist office filing.
- Attend meeting and write meeting minutes.
- Assist for loan investigation.
- Perform other relevant duties as requested by the supervisor.

Academic Qualification:

I have completed MBA (HRM) from Southeast University, 2016 in 3.11 CGPA and MBS (Management) from Tejgaon College under National University, 2015 in 2nd class.

Certificate Course: Post Graduation Diploma in Human Resource Management (BIM) – 2019

Computer Literacy : MS-Word, MS-Excel, Power Point, Internet browsing & data management.

Language & Other Activities:

- Proficient in both Bengali and English.
- Excellent communication and Teamwork Skills, Hardworking, Quick learner, Competitive, Interested with new ideas and amiable.
- 6th month Merchandising certificate course at BGMEA.
- Photography course at PATHSHALA SOUTH ASIAN MEDIA INSTITUTE.
- Involved with YMCA & Catenian Association.

Personal Information:

Father's NameMother's NameChristopher CorrayaProvati G. Rozario

• Present Address : Anwara Garden, 105/3-6, Block-A, Flat-3A, Tejkunipara, Tejgaon,

Dhaka - 1215

• Permanent Address : 48 South Begun Bari, Christian Para, Tejgaon, Dhaka - 1208

Date of Birth
 15th January 1986
 Nationality
 Bangladeshi (by birth)

Religion : ChristianMarital status : Married

• Interest : Reading books, Photography, Watching movies, Traveling,

Listening and Socializing with various people.

Reference:

1. Md. Asiful Hoque

General Manger - Bangladesh Operations Stichting Bangladesh Accord Foundation Floor-12, AJ Hieghts, Cha-72/1/D, Pragati Sarani, North Badda, Dhaka-1212, Bangladesh

 $\underline{asiful hoque@hotmail.com}$

Contact: 01711-539135

2. Md. Qamrul Ahsan ACA

AGM (Accounts) Ha-Meem Group

387, Tejgaon I/A, Dhaka – 1208

ahsanrobel@yahoo.com Contact: 01727-346733

Signati	ure			